<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sunflower Dash</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/</link><description>Recent content on Sunflower Dash</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sunflower Dash - Bees and Wasps</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/bees-and-wasps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/bees-and-wasps/</guid><description> Bees sting and pop the ball They evolve and turn into wasps Wasps have a quicker attack and have a longer flight range also have a more lethal sting Bees have a limited flight range Knock bees out with fly swatters Bees have one stinger but wasps have three Stings absorbed by bee amunity Each wasp sting absorbed by three amunity Bees and wasps wear top hats Wasps are bigger than bees</description></item><item><title>Sunflower Dash - Butterfly</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/butterfly/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/butterfly/</guid><description> Butterflys pick you up You fly for 10 seconds You do not control butterflys Butterflys move randomly they can go up, down, backwards, and forwards</description></item><item><title>Sunflower Dash - Flowers</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/flowers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/flowers/</guid><description>Flowers
Sunflowers are the main flower that you will see throughout the game. Some sunflowers will be wilted and collapse 1 second after contact with the ball. Bellflowers catapult you forward into the air and you will fly for 5 seconds. Swaying sunflowers sway in the wind and you have to calculate when to jump on them. Dandelions let off dandelion seeds that carry you through the air.</description></item><item><title>Sunflower Dash - Game Design</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/game-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/game-design/</guid><description> Player is a beach ball bouncing on sunflowers Your currency in the game are flower petals and stars (stars are more valuable than flower petals) Flower color are the colors in your color inventory (you slowly collect them while you play) Some sunflowers sway from side to side Evil bees and worms eat or pop ball Butterflies and dandelion seeds carry you around The floor is covered with goatheads or/and cacti There are gopher holes that you can use to escape the obstacles but you have to watch out for the gopher that will chase you down the tunnels in the gopher holes In the shop you can buy a bee protective shield or 3 bee shields make one wasp shield There are wasps and they can sting faster and have a longer distance range You can customize your beach ball in the shop using flower colors for custom design or you can buy pre-made designs using flower petals Bell flowers can catapult you forward Some sunflowers go up and down Thorny goatheads pop you Game art</description></item><item><title>Sunflower Dash - Petals</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/petals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/petals/</guid><description> Petals are like money. You can get things from the shop with them. You get flower petels when you run into them. Petals are yellow You get one on sun flowers,two on bell flowers,and one on butterflies. You don&amp;rsquo;t get one petal on every flower. If you get rainbow petals you can get any thing in the shop. Rainbow petals are very rare. Big petals are 3 small petals.</description></item><item><title>Sunflower Dash - Shop</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/shop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/shop/</guid><description> In the shop you can get potions, baseball bats and new skins. You get things from the shop with petals. You can upgrade baseball bats into chain saws. Potions are 10 petals, new skins are 10 - 100, baseball bats are 15.</description></item><item><title>Sunflower Dash - Things on the ground</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/things-on-the-ground/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/things-on-the-ground/</guid><description> trampolines make you bounce goatheads make your beach ball pop rocks you lose some air snakes toss you back up to the flowers gum makes you stick to the ground</description></item><item><title>Sunflower Dash - Types of sunflowers</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/types_of_sunflowers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/types_of_sunflowers/</guid><description>The sunflowers will have faces that show if they are healthy/alive, eaten, or wilted.
There are many different types of sunflower. Here are a few:
Regular sunflowers have happy faces and stand still and don&amp;rsquo;t do anything exept wilt over a set period time. Face:O O U Wilted sunflowers will break if you sit on them for too long. When they wilt, they will be bent over and have a brownish tint and look sick.</description></item><item><title>Sunflower Dash - Underground</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/underground/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/underground/</guid><description> Bottles are a quick way to get underground. Sleeping gophers chase you when you walk into the tunnel. If you have a snail shell you can disguise and walk right past the sleeping gophers. Gophers chase you until you get out of the tunnel. Worms make small tunnels that you can escape from the gophers. Worms will pop you if you get too close to them.</description></item><item><title>Sunflowers</title><link>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/sunflowers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://temperate-designs.github.io/sunflower-dash/sunflowers/</guid><description> Not all Sunflowers behave the same way. Some Sunflowers stay still. Sunflowers go up and down and side to side. The flower petals are floating in the air and you need to jump to get them.</description></item></channel></rss>